#### Contact

07876801649 (Mobile) Noahkayodeojo@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/noah-ojo-067307253 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Clinical Microbiology Serology automated machine

#### Honors-Awards

Na You I Praise-Kaystrings -Best Worship Song Of the Year

Most Experience Nigerian Music Producer of the Year 2021

# **NOAH OJO**

Music Professional / Director Stardom / Music Artist / Scientist Gillingham, England, United Kingdom

# Summary

I am a Professional, creative, enthusiastic and reliable music Producer/Mixing and Mastering Engineer (Online Berklee School Of Music) who has over 12 years of experience in multiple genres and areas of sound production. With a good understanding of the music industry and a number of contacts and collaborations around music world. Award winning, A multi-instrumentalist with a background in individual, group and/or instrumental music Creation for Concerts Commercials, Reality TV Shows E.t.c. Confident in sound design and music composition. Dedicated to constantly learning and developing new skills in the audio world, with a passion for technology. I also have a degree microbiology and practiced as Food Health and Safety Scientist / Medical lab-scientist in which i have derived the ability to be self motivated with a commitment to achieving high standards and results. Able to identify and learn new skills and manage resources effectively to meet targets. Deep concern about health and safety measures, A fast learner, Teachable, highly flexible with excellent adaptability to new environments, an effective communicator, with a commitment to service.

# Experience

Self-employed

Music Professional

Notes Inc. Media / Stardom Nigeria Season 1 Music Director August 2018 - Present (4 years 3 months) Nigeria/ Austria

 As Music Director, I designed model for the Tv reality show Stardom Nigeria a music reality tv show the that coach and mentor 3 categories of musician Vocalist Song Writer and Music Producer from different part of Nigeria all at once to compete for a winning price.

- I coordinated and scheduled all tasks every week, performances for every group musical group. In cooperation with the organizer of Stardom Nigeria. (Notes Inc Media from Austria)
- Plan and select different genre of music that the groups will write, arrange,
   record and then perform on the show every week
- As Music Producer coach I trained the music producers 3 times a week about music productions of different genre to improve their skills while on the show.

Cobhams Asuquo Music Production Audio Engineer June 2015 - Present (7 years 5 months) United States

Timeless by Omawumi ft Anjelic Kidjo (Grammy Award Winning)

 Engineered and recorded most songs on this album (in South Africa and Nigeria) in collaboration with other music producer from all around the globe;
 Paul (226 Recording Huston United States), Adam Howard (Howard Audio South Africa)

Companies, Commercial, Ngo(s) and Organizations;

- # NBC(Coke a Cola)-Share A Coke A Cola Campaign 2014.
- # Nigerian Brewery-OH Maltina 2016.
- # MTN PROJECT FAME: Theme Song Season 7 2014.
- # NBC Copa Coca Cola 2016 Theme Song
- # Guaranty Trust Bank(GTBank)- 737 Campaign. 2016
- # MTN Foundation-10th Year Anniversary, Yello Campaign.
- # Project Fame (Season 7 Theme song)

After Dark Music Entertainment (Music Director/Band Leader Guitarist)

Music Director/Band Leader Guitarist April 2014 - Present (8 years 7 months) Nigeria

- Select and Audition Musician, Back up Singers for tours and weekly events
- Choose and arrange songs/repeteurs for artist
- Call for weekly rehearsals and brain storming sessions
- · Record mix and master performances, tours and events

Xtreame Entertainment by Ice Nweke (Creative Director Ballroom & latin coach and TapDancer)

Music Performace

2013 - Present (9 years)

Lagos, Nigeria

- Produce, Record, Create Sound design Mix and Master the entire shows music
- · Work Closely with Stage directors, Choreographers Actors and Singers
- Perform Composition with Band live on the Show

Azusa Recordings Ng.(GraceHill Recordings), Lagos/Abuja, Nigeria. Audio Engineer

June 2010 - Present (12 years 5 months)

Nigeria

# Oversee production of project from beginning to end, in most cases includes some or all of these process carried out in and out of the country. (Production, Co-Production, Engineer, Voice Over, Writing, Recording, Mixing and/or Mastering)

# Assist in Song Writing and Creative Contents of the projects.

# Good Knowledge of the use of multiple Daws (Protools, Cubsase, Luna, Logic, Main Stage Native instrument e.t.c) and sound design plugins and synths

# Also gained in this time a vast knowledge of Video production, graphics and photography from Story boarding to the effects and final output

# Play guitar regularly for studio session and collaborate with different artist around the world

Reddington Multispecialist Hospital

4 years

Certified Phlebotomist/ Laboratory Scientist June 2010 - June 2013 (3 years 1 month)

Lagos, Nigeria

- Assure that all collection instruments and environments are sterile and of first use.
- Correctly labeling the collection container with pertinent patient information for identification.
- Blood collection from patients and preservation
- · Blood collection from donors

- Complete and file companion paperwork to trace the route of the sample from collection through lab work through final analysis and diagnosis and finally to proper disposal of the fluids.
- Transport of Blood samples to the laboratory for analysis
- Train other phlebotomists in sample collection and follow up.

Laboratory Scientist Reddington Multispecialist Hospital. (NYSC)

July 2009 - July 2010 (1 year 1 month)

Lagos, Nigeria

- Collection, inspection of specimens at reception and Patients data Imputation
- Sample collation, labeling, preparation for analysis and referral for specialist testing
- Assisting in analysis of samples using automated machinery and manual techniques
- · Assisting in writing of SOP in departments without one and analyzers
- Ensures HSE requirements.
- Working in the administrative dept which involves registration and referrals
- Working in the phlebotomy room where you relate to patients and where blood samples are collected.
- Laboratory analysis in the following department: Histopathology, Cytology, Hematology, Chemical pathology, Endocrinology, Microbiology, Serology, Cardiology and Microbiology using automated machinery and manual techniques

National Agency for Food and Drug Administration and Control (NAFDAC)

Laboratory Scientist at: National Agency for Food Drug Administration and Control (NAFDAC)

May 2007 - December 2007 (8 months)

Nigeria

Head of Industrial Training Department

- Collection, inspection of specimens at reception
- Sample collation, labeling, preparation for analysis and referral for specialist testing
- Assisting in analysis of samples using automated machinery and manual techniques
- Ensures HSE requirements.

- Culturing different types of samples e.g. food, water, drugs and various samples
- Carried out environmental monitoring analysis of the laboratory

#### Administravtive duties:

- Drawing up a Rosta to ensure a proper flow of work
- Managing of personnel
- Assisting in writing of Departmental SOP
- Writing daily report and reporting results

# Education

### Berklee College of Music

Certificate, Advanced Mixing and Mastering Protools · (April 2015 - September 2015)

### University of Port Harcourt

Bachelor of Science - BS, Microbiology, General · (June 2003 - August 2008)

## Rick Denis Computer College

High School Diploma, Computer and Information Sciences and Support Services · (April 2002 - July 2002)